That is an adorable cat.
Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, too.
Beautiful.
Indeed.
Reminds me of the sky over Sark.
The sky there was really pretty, too.
That was right after we met.
We're almost there.
Kagami Aoi's perfect and beautiful
FC is almost within our grasp.
Her Angelic Halo...
Captivated by the beauty of its dazzling
light, we've pursued it ever since.
All this time, we've striven
to get closer to it.
And to surpass it.
This view reminds me of all our struggles.
And our efforts will soon be rewarded, Saki.
Yes,
Irina.
Episode Ten:
"Is That For FC, Too?"
Now give me one more lap.
Okay!
We have to run even more?!
Trail running is the ideal
way to develop the stamina,
lower-body strength, and jumping
ability required for FC.
And there's more.
Coping with unpaved and uneven ground
will help you recover your
posture during dogfights.
Inui-san always controls
her opponents' positions,
so we need to work this hard to
drag her into a dogfight, I guess.
I ran out of stamina during
the summer tournament,
so I need to work on my conditioning.
Okay, I'll set the pace for the next lap.
Follow me!
Okay, Former Captain!
I'm gonna win this time, too!
Wait for me!
What're you even doing here, Bro?
What purpose does this training serve?
Swimming puts your entire
body's muscles to equal use,
so it's the perfect way to
refine membrane control.
And training underwater will
also improve lung capacity.
It's basically a more
strenuous dogfight of sorts.
That's so pretty, Asuka-senpai!
On your marks...
Set!
Okay, I'll go next—
Go home already. You've got
college entrance exams to study for.
Quit forcing me to face reality!
It appears you're pushing them pretty hard.
That brings back memories.
Back when you'd just picked up FC,
you were having that much
fun flying around, too.
Their faces reminded me of that.
Let's call it a day.
After you get home,
be sure to do your stretches before bed.
Good work!
This is the first time in my life
I've ever put in this much effort.
Should I get some running in before bed, too?
Get a hold of yourself, Asuka-senpai!
There isn't much time left
before the fall tournament,
so we'll have to focus on
FC throughout the breaks.
Practice starts at 6 AM tomorrow.
Got it, Coach.
Think you can wake up for it, Misaki?
6 AM? Seriously?
It'll be fine!
I'll come wake you up as always,
so feel free to sleep soundly.
No! I'll wake up by myself tomorrow!
Whoa, she's extra-motivated!
Way to go, Misaki-chan!
The Birdcage isn't the only
thing Inui has going for her.
We won't be able to cope with her unless
we have several tricks up our sleeve.
Apart from the current practice regimen,
is there anything else I
can do to help the team?
What can I do for them?
Safe...
I showed the alarm clock...
who's boss!
It's a miracle!
I went to wake Misaki-senpai up, but...
Good morning.
Guess that goes to show how
much I wanna play FC right now.
Asuka?
Good morning!
Morning.
You came early?
Yes. I've been here since before dawn.
D-Dawn?
That's beyond early!
I'm just so happy I can fly again.
Sorry.
Well, it's nothing to apologize for.
Masaya!
Let's start practice right away!
O-Okay!
Don't you think they'll be pretty
competitive against Inui-san right now?
Yeah.
They've shown definite improvement
in their stamina and fundamentals,
which are crucial in a match.
But dealing with Inui's
perfectly planned movements
will require more flexible
offensive and defensive skills.
Unfortunately, we don't have enough
people to train those efficiently.
Oh...
Well, we're not a large team like Takafuji.
Whatcha doing, Mashiro?
I'm calibrating my Grav-shoes for fighter use
so I can dogfight with you later.
There!
All done!
Cleared fur takeoff!
Mashiro-cchi!
Mashiro?!
Spread your arms and legs wide and relax!
Okay...
That nearly gave me a heart attack!
You forgot to switch on the balancer
after calibrating it, didn't you?
R-Right...
You pulled off some amazing
moves just now, Mashiro-chan.
Uh, it wasn't on purpose, you know.
I want to try spinning at full speed, too!
A-Are you serious?!
Hey, Asuka!
Are you sure about this?
I am!
Be careful.
I will.
Fly!
Wh-Whoa!
Wait, why are you fighting it?
Well, uh, how do I put this...
Remember, Asuka-senpai! High-speed spinning!
Here I go!
Spread your limbs as far wide as you can!
Wow, I can't even fly straight.
Balancers reduce your Grav-shoes' sensitivity,
which makes it easier to fly.
So if you turn them off,
the Grav-shoes will be responsive
to finer membrane control,
but you'll lose all stability and
be unable to even fly straight.
So it's kinda like taking
a spacewalk without an MMU?
S-Something like that, yeah.
Anyway, let's get back to practice.
Okay!
That's Europe's top players for you.
They make for great sparring partners.
Saki,
unlock your balancer.
To the first phase?
No, you've already perfected
its use at 50 percent unlocked.
Let's proceed to the next phase.
Okay.
Phase second...
100 percent unlocked.
Wow, I can't believe you woke
up early two days in a row!
It's a miracle!
I hope hell doesn't freeze over
and make bad things happen!
Lay off.
Today, let's start with practice matches—
This voice...
Could it be?
S-Satouin-san?
Why a fishing boat?
See? Something bad did happen!
It's not my fault.
Greetings, ladies and gentlemen.
Good morning.
M-Morning.
Thank you for coming all
this way, Satouin-san.
What? You called for them?
Yes.
I texted them to ask if they wanted in.
Asuka?
Now, then, Kurashina Asuka.
You're challenging me to
the rematch we agreed on
when we first met, I take it?
Very well!
You want to duel me with the
fall tournament approaching?
I applaud your guts.
I've brought Ichinose-san
to act as our witness,
so let us fight fair and square!
Th-That wasn't what I meant!
I was just asking if you wanted
to join us for practice.
What?
I-I see how it is.
So we use this opportunity to
see how each of us is doing,
and save the rematch for the tournament?
Pleased to be working with you again.
I'm glad we can practice together once more.
Let's have fun, Mashiro.
Thank you.
The more sparring partners we have,
the better prepared we'll be to take on Inui.
Of course, I intend to
take down Inui Saki, too.
Captain Shindou's honor shall be avenged
by none other than myself,
Satouin Reiko!
Sh-She's awfully fired up.
Switch.
Next up, Asuka.
Got it!
We're on standby.
Okay!
Listen up, Asuka.
You have to slip through
those three's attacks
and touch the second buoy.
The time limit is two minutes.
Got it!
Okay, Satouin-san,
Ichinose-san, and Mashiro-chan...
Let's do this.
Set!
I'm going in!
There!
Got you!
You're wide open!
No way!
She dodged it?
It's practically impossible
to see attacks from above.
That's pretty scary, if you ask me.
Inui's FC is all about maintaining
that position of dominance.
I did it!
Asuka-chan's amazing.
Tell me about it.
Asuka really is amazing.
But I have to aim much, much higher.
I need to visit the drugstore.
What's wrong?
I kind of sprained my wrist.
Huh? Where's the new captain?
Madoka went back home to check
whether Shion-senpai is studying
as he should be.
She sure has it rough.
Let's wrap up early today
so you can get some rest.
Okay.
See you tomorrow, then.
You're going home already?
What about udon?
I'll pass today. Sorry.
I'm in the mood for udon with meat.
Can I come have some?
Yeah, yeah!
Oh, it's a kitty cat.
U-U—
Um...
Wh-What are you doing here?
I came to see her.
I can't keep her at the dorm.
Is that so?
That's an adorable kitty cat.
Mind if I pet her?
Go ahead.
Come here.
She hates me.
She's a shy one.
Don't let it bother you.
I guess.
Oh, right!
Thank you for playing me the other day.
I'm really sorry I wasn't able to
put up much of a fight, though.
But I'm practicing really
hard right now so I can have
an exciting match with you next time.
So look forward to the fall tournament—
That's out of the question.
Mine and Irina's FC is not like yours.
We'll always be the ones winning.
Inui-san...
Is that for FC, too?
Of course.
At times, it is necessary
to have a clear mind.
Satouin-san told me that you're
training yourself here now.
What do you want?
I want you to teach me FC.
Why me?
You said before that you enjoy
being in a state of fear.
I want to know how fun fear can be.
Well, then.
Where should we begin?
Where'd you go yesterday, Misaki-senpai?
I sent you ten whole
messages filled with love!
Sorry. I had some stuff going on.
How's your wrist, Asuka?
It's all right now.
You heal fast when you're young.
You sound like the friendly
neighborhood housewife, New Captain.
Seriously, enough with the "new" alread—
Good morning.
Allow me to join you.
I asked him.
Let's have some fun.
Strategy meeting to decide
on a tactical game plan vs. Inui Saki
Menacing
High yo-yo
Beating Inui Saki.
We've practiced as hard as we could,
focusing on just that one goal.
Satouin-san, Ichinose-san,
and even Shindou-san
are giving Asuka and the rest a helping hand.
So I...
Is that the answer you found?
Yes.
I want to do everything
I can to help them, too!
I see.
Very well.
I'm off.
Masaya...
This is nothing!
Shindou-san's imitating Inui-san's movements.
He mastered them after just one look?
That's the King of Kings for you.
Feral combat instincts...
You're starting to display an
asset Kurashina-kun doesn't have.
Thank you very much!
Misaki...
You're getting too worked up and
losing track of your surroundings.
Coach?!
Hinata-kun?
Those Grav-shoes...
Asuka!
Y-Yes?
Take me on in a dogfight.
Try to score a point, even if you
have to throw the kitchen sink at me!
Got it!
Fly!
Things are getting kinda crazy.
That move...
Sonic Boost, similar to
Inui-kun's sudden elevation.
An explosive acceleration move that uses
slight movements to trim the membrane.
Hinata-kun had already mastered
it back in grade school.
Welcome home, Masaya.
You're too predictable!
Try more things to confuse your opponent!
O-Okay!
If your opponent's heading you off,
use a Sonic Boost to evade to shake them off!
Amazing.
I've got your back—
I-Incredible!
What was that move?
Blaster Roll.
Together with Sonic Boost from earlier,
they were originally
Kagami-sensei's special moves.
Kagami-sensei's?
I wanted to be like her.
And I wanted to use the same moves
she did, so I begged her to teach me.
She put me through sheer hell, though.
Want me to remind you...
of that hell once more?
All of you, come at me together.
I'll teach you my ace in the hole.
Our FC is beautiful.
Just as Kagami Aoi's play style was.
We'll bring the world to its knees
and make it admit
our perfect FC is superior
to that circus imitation.
To Be Continued
Preview
What do I say?
How's that? Did it fire you up some?
You're so cool, Misaki-chan!
Episode Eleven:
"I Refuse to Lose!"
I refuse to lose!